Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
TYPHOON FAMILY
عائلة تايفون
Ms. Oh!
السيدة أوه!
-Mr. Go!
-سيدي انطلق!
-My gosh, Mr. Go!
-يا إلهي، سيد جو! -سيد جو!
-Okay.
-سيد اذهب! -حسنًا.
-What do we do?
-ماذا نفعل؟ -حسنا.
-We get it. -Ms. Oh! Please help…
-فهمنا. -سيدتي. أوه! أرجوكِ ساعديني...
Don't give up on me!
لا تتخلى عني!
-Let's go! -Help me!
-هيا بنا! -ساعدني!
-Wait…
-انتظر…
I'm innocent!
أنا بريء!
-Mr. Go… -I'm not guilty!
-سيد جو... -أنا لست مذنبًا!
Man, why are the roaches here so big?
يا رجل، لماذا الصراصير هنا كبيرة جدًا؟
-Do we have the number? -Yes, I had it written down.
-هل لدينا الرقم؟ -نعم، لقد كتبته.
Where is it?
أين هي؟
KOREAN EMBASSY
السفارة الكورية
-Look, here. -Is this it?
-انظر هنا. -هل هذا هو؟
Hello, this is the Korean Embassy in Thailand. How can I help you?
مرحباً، هذه السفارة الكورية في تايلاند. كيف يمكنني مساعدتك؟
Hello, we are a company called Typhoon Trading from Korea.
مرحباً، نحن شركة تدعى Typhoon Trading من كوريا.
One of my staff is being held at the detention center.
أحد موظفيّ محتجز في مركز الاحتجاز.
Okay, what was the reason for their detention?
حسنًا، ما هو سبب احتجازهم؟
I hear it's for bribery, but the sum was almost nothing.
سمعت أنها كانت بسبب الرشوة، لكن المبلغ كان لا شيء تقريبًا.
Did you bribe an official?
هل رشوت مسؤولا؟
I understand, but it's just $50.
أنا أفهم ذلك، ولكن سعره 50 دولارًا فقط.
Please contact the embassy only in urgent situations.
يرجى الاتصال بالسفارة فقط في الحالات العاجلة.
Yes, that's exactly the kind of situation we're in.
نعم، هذا هو بالضبط نوع الوضع الذي نحن فيه.
If it was just $50, they'll be released soon.
لو كان سعرها 50 دولار فقط، فسيتم إصدارها قريبًا.
A criminal offence…
جريمة جنائية…
Why did you hang up?
لماذا أغلقت الهاتف؟
What did they say?
ماذا قالوا؟
-The cold hard truth. -What?
-الحقيقة القاسية الباردة. -ماذا؟
Oh, gosh.
يا إلهي.
I shouldn't have given him that money.
لا ينبغي لي أن أعطيه هذا المال.
WE ARE OPEN
نحن مفتوحون
About my uncle.
عن عمي.
He's bald and bold.
إنه أصلع وجريء.
Can you believe he filled half that bag with his care package for Ma-yong?
هل يمكنك أن تصدق أنه ملأ نصف تلك الحقيبة بحزمة الرعاية الخاصة به لما يونغ؟
Mind you, that's a huge suitcase expats use to travel.
انتبه، فهذه حقيبة ضخمة يستخدمها المغتربون للسفر.
I'm back at my old company.
لقد عدت إلى شركتي القديمة.
I'm really determined…
أنا مصمم حقا...
to give it my all this time.
لأعطي كل ما لدي هذه المرة.
So, don't you worry about me.
لذا لا تقلق علي.
Okay, then.
حسنا إذن.
I'll get going now.
سأذهب الآن.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
I can't believe it. Not again.
لا أصدق ذلك. ليس مرة أخرى.
Take it.
خذها.
You'll have to treat Ma-yong to a meal or something.
سيتعين عليك دعوة ما يونغ لتناول وجبة أو شيء من هذا القبيل.
That's how you win goodwill.
بهذه الطريقة تكسب حسن النية.
This is the first US dollar bill I've ever held in my hand.
هذه هي أول ورقة نقدية من فئة الدولار الأمريكي أحملها في يدي على الإطلاق.
Thanks to you, son.
شكرا لك يا ابني.
SHOE REPAIR SPECIALIST OPEN DAILY FROM 7:00 A.M. TO 6:00 P.M.
متخصص في إصلاح الأحذية مفتوح يوميًا من الساعة 7:00 صباحًا حتى 6:00 مساءً
That bill meant so much to me.
لقد كان هذا القانون يعني الكثير بالنسبة لي.
You must be Korean.
يجب أن تكون كوريًا.
What was that?
ماذا كان هذا؟
I worked in Korea for four years in Gwangju, Gyeonggi-do.
لقد عملت في كوريا لمدة أربع سنوات في مدينة جوانججو، مقاطعة جيونج جي.
You seem like an upstanding guy.
يبدو أنك رجل مستقيم.
How did you end up here?
كيف انتهى بك الأمر هنا؟
Well, I'm in for bribery.
حسنًا، أنا متورط في الرشوة.
You bribed someone?
هل رشوت أحدا؟
-Who? -A customs officer at Lamchaya Port.
-من؟ -موظف جمارك في ميناء لامشايا.
By the way, how old are you to talk so casually to me?
بالمناسبة، كم عمرك حتى تتحدث معي بهذه البساطة؟
I'm 48 years old. I'm old enough.
عمري 48 سنة. أنا كبير السن بما فيه الكفاية.
A customs officer at Lamchaya Port.
موظف جمارك في ميناء لامشايا.
What did he just say?
ماذا قال للتو؟
-There will be a trial early tomorrow. -A trial? All right.
-ستكون هناك محاكمة مبكرة غدًا. -محاكمة؟ حسنًا.
-It's for those who bribed a small amount. -A small amount. Got it.
-هذا لمن دفع رشوة بسيطة. -مبلغ بسيط. فهمت.
As in any payments under $200.
كما هو الحال في أي مدفوعات أقل من 200 دولار.
Under $200? Of course, I should've known.
أقل من ٢٠٠ دولار؟ بالطبع، كان ينبغي عليّ أن أعرف.
It made no sense to get dragged here for chump change.
لم يكن من المنطقي أن يتم جلبي إلى هنا مقابل مبلغ زهيد.
I'll be released tomorrow then.
سيتم إطلاق سراحي غدًا إذن.
What's your name? My name is Go Ma-jin.
ما اسمك؟ اسمي غو ما جين.
I'm Somchai. Somchai Saroon.
أنا سومتشاي. سومتشاي سارون.
Somchai? Your name reminds me of som tam.
سومتشاي؟ اسمك يذكرني بسوم تام.
Hang in there, all right?
استمر في الصمود، حسنًا؟
I like your style.
انا احب اسلوبك.
You think I've got style?
هل تعتقد أن لدي أسلوب؟
I guess you like my jacket. This is my everyday look.
أظن أن سترتي تعجبك. هذا مظهري اليومي.
Anyway, it's a pleasure.
على أية حال، إنه لمن دواعي سروري.
Things will turn around, so don't ever lose your spirit.
سوف تتغير الأمور، لذلك لا تفقد روحك أبدًا.
I can rest easy now.
أستطيع أن أرتاح بسهولة الآن.
I'm going to sleep.
سأذهب للنوم.
Jeez.
جيز.
I'm getting out.
انا اخرج.
Gosh.
يا إلهي.
Tomorrow?
غداً؟
Thank goodness.
شكرا لله.
The newly elected governor made a thorough sweep
أجرى الحاكم المنتخب حديثًا عملية تمشيط شاملة
to stamp out corruption in the local government.
للقضاء على الفساد في الحكومة المحلية.
Still, any bribe under 10,000 baht is seen as a misdemeanor
مع ذلك، فإن أي رشوة أقل من 10000 بات تعتبر جنحة.
and can receive a summary judgment.
ويمكن أن يحصل على حكم موجز.
He'll likely be released with a fine at most.
ومن المرجح أن يتم إطلاق سراحه مع دفع غرامة على الأكثر.
How much would the fine be?
كم سيكون مقدار الغرامة؟
Around 100,000 baht, so about 3,000,000 won.
حوالي 100 ألف بات، أي حوالي 3 ملايين وون.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
what about the meeting with Nihakham Group as our potential client?
ماذا عن اللقاء مع مجموعة نهاكم كعميل محتمل لدينا؟
I don't think you can make a comeback from today's mishap.
لا أعتقد أنك قادر على العودة من حادث اليوم.
-What?
-ماذا؟
You see, this incident made the headlines of every newspaper and news show.
كما ترون، فقد تصدرت هذه الحادثة عناوين جميع الصحف والبرامج الإخبارية.
What's more, Chairman Nihakham is a stickler for rules.
علاوة على ذلك، يعتبر الرئيس نيهكهام متشددًا في الالتزام بالقواعد.
Oh, dear.
يا عزيزي.
The whole thing has turned into a pain in the neck, hasn't it?
لقد تحول الأمر برمته إلى ألم في الرقبة، أليس كذلك؟
It's not so dire.
إنه ليس خطيرا جدا.
Once Mr. Go is released and we get our goods,
بمجرد إطلاق سراح السيد جو وحصولنا على بضائعنا،
we can sell them, right?
يمكننا بيعها، أليس كذلك؟
-Bangkok has six million residents! -That's true.
-يبلغ عدد سكان بانكوك ستة ملايين نسمة! -هذا صحيح.
We can sell our goods.
نحن نستطيع بيع بضائعنا.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Goodness.
الخير.
I'd say you seem pretty agitated.
أعتقد أنك تبدو مضطربًا جدًا.
What?
ماذا؟
No, it was nothing. You can sit back down.
لا، لم يكن شيئًا. يمكنك الجلوس مجددًا.
-Come on, it's hard to look up at you. -Calm down and take a seat, Mr. Kang.
- تعال، من الصعب أن أنظر إليك. - اهدأ واجلس، سيد كانج.
Hey, I got it!
مهلا، لقد حصلت عليه!
Five times one is five
خمسة في واحد يساوي خمسة
Five times two is ten
خمسة في اثنين يساوي عشرة
Attaboy. Keep it going.
أحسنت. استمر.
Five times three is fifteen
خمسة في ثلاثة يساوي خمسة عشر
Five times four is twenty
خمسة في أربعة يساوي عشرين
Five times five is…
خمسة في خمسة يساوي…
What's five times five?
ما هو خمسة في خمسة؟
Five times five…
خمسة مرات خمسة…
Five times five is 35!
خمسة في خمسة يساوي 35!
From the top.
من الأعلى.
I thought the department store doesn't open today.
اعتقدت أن المتجر لن يفتح اليوم.
Has your older sister given you a call…
هل اتصلت بك أختك الكبرى؟
I guess she hasn't.
أعتقد أنها لم تفعل ذلك.
Well…
حسنًا…
This is… You know, take them.
هذا... كما تعلم، خذهم.
What was that? I didn't catch that at all.
ماذا كان هذا؟ لم أفهم ذلك إطلاقًا.
-What are those? -A present for me.
-ما هي هذه؟ -هدية لي.
-Let me do it, ma'am. -What?
- دعيني أفعل ذلك سيدتي. - ماذا؟
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Why did you bring out the heavy comforters for winter?
لماذا أخرجت الأغطية الثقيلة لفصل الشتاء؟
They're cotton-filled comforters to keep my grandchildren warm.
إنها عبارة عن لحاف مملوء بالقطن لإبقاء أحفادي دافئين.
I'm sure I still have a long time to stay on this earth,
أنا متأكد من أن لدي وقتا طويلا للبقاء على هذه الأرض،
but I always feel like I'm on a tight schedule.
لكني أشعر دائمًا أنني ملتزم بجدول زمني ضيق.
There we go.
هناك نذهب.
Let's start.
لنبدأ.
MOMO'S PUB
حانة مومو
Come on in.
تفضل بالدخول.
Welcome.
مرحباً.
Here. Please take a seat.
تفضل بالجلوس هنا.
I brought a lunchbox.
لقد أحضرت صندوق الغداء.
I've never done this before.
لم أفعل هذا من قبل .
-Is this for me? -You can have it all.
-هل هذا من أجلي؟ -يمكنك الحصول على كل شيء.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
The place looks different during the day.
المكان يبدو مختلفا خلال النهار.
Didn't you say you run the place with your mother?
ألم تقل أنك تدير المكان مع والدتك؟
My dear Ms. Kim Eul-nyeo owns this place,
عزيزتي السيدة كيم يول نيو تمتلك هذا المكان،
but she's been away often lately.
لكنها كانت بعيدة كثيرًا في الآونة الأخيرة.
I guess she's busy.
أعتقد أنها مشغولة.
I can't say.
لا أستطيع أن أقول.
-How long do you work daily? -Me?
-كم من الوقت تعمل يوميا؟ -أنا؟
We keep the place open for ten hours.
نبقي المكان مفتوحا لمدة عشر ساعات.
With ingredient prep and cleaning, I work about 12 to 13 hours.
مع تحضير المكونات والتنظيف، أعمل لمدة تتراوح بين 12 إلى 13 ساعة.
Business hasn't been so great, so I might have to pick up other jobs.
لم تكن الأعمال جيدة جدًا، لذا قد أضطر إلى البحث عن وظائف أخرى.
-Other jobs? -Yes.
-وظائف أخرى؟ -نعم.
By the way, with a business of this size, doesn't that mean the owner is well-off?
بالمناسبة، مع عمل تجاري بهذا الحجم، ألا يعني هذا أن المالك ثري؟
Since this is your mother's place, you're her heir.
بما أن هذا هو مكان والدتك، فأنت وريثها.
Hey, you're rich, Nam-mo.
مهلا، أنت غني، نام مو.
My dear Mi-ho, you'll probably swoon if you meet an actually rich person.
عزيزتي مي هو، من المحتمل أن تصابي بالذهول إذا قابلت شخصًا ثريًا حقًا.
Don't be silly.
لا تكن سخيفا.
I've met plenty of rich people!
لقد قابلت الكثير من الأشخاص الأثرياء!
Really?
حقًا؟
You know what?
أتعلم؟
You're so pretty.
أنت جميلة جدًا.
Give me a second. I'll whip up a tasty snack.
أعطني ثانية. سأحضر لك وجبة خفيفة لذيذة.
Where are his suitcases?
أين حقائبه؟
Let's get him some clothes to change into after his release tomorrow.
دعونا نحضر له بعض الملابس ليغيرها بعد إطلاق سراحه غدًا.
He only had an undershirt underneath the jacket.
كان يرتدي فقط قميصًا داخليًا أسفل السترة.
Okay.
تمام.
Hey, the collar is all stretched.
مهلا، تم تمديد كل طوق.
-That even has a hole. -That too.
-حتى أنه يوجد به ثقب. -هذا أيضًا.
Jeez, Mr. Go enjoyed a snack all alone.
يا إلهي، لقد استمتع السيد جو بوجبة خفيفة بمفرده.
SPICY TUNA
تونة حارة
Mr. Kang.
السيد كانغ.
Look.
ينظر.
KIMCHI RAMYUN, NEMO RAMYUN, BRAVO TUNA, SPICY TUNA
كيمتشي راميون، نيمو راميون، برافو تونا، تونا سبايسي
He packed more to share with us.
لقد حزم المزيد ليشاركه معنا.
He brought three items each.
لقد أحضر كل واحد منهم ثلاثة أشياء.
MIN BURI CRIMINAL COURT MIN BURI CIVIL COURT
محكمة مين بوري الجنائية محكمة مين بوري المدنية
I don't get it.
انا لم احصل عليها.
-Why can't we go in? -Be patient, Mr. Kang.
-لماذا لا نستطيع الدخول؟ -تحل بالصبر يا سيد كانج.
We're looking into it.
نحن نبحث في الأمر.
Hey, there's Ha-neul.
مرحبًا، هناك ها-نول.
Get over here.
تعال إلى هنا.
-Be careful. -Let's see.
- كن حذرا. - دعنا نرى.
"Ten thousand dollars"?
"عشرة آلاف دولار"؟
It says you bribed $10,000, not $50.
يقول أنك دفعت رشوة قدرها 10000 دولار، وليس 50 دولارًا.
What? They think Mr. Go did that?
ماذا؟ يعتقدون أن السيد جو فعل ذلك؟
Wait, $10,000 equals over 15 million won.
انتظر، 10000 دولار تساوي أكثر من 15 مليون وون.
I don't get it, either.
أنا أيضا لا أفهم ذلك.
That must be why Ma-jin wasn't included in the trial.
لا بد أن هذا هو السبب وراء عدم إدراج ما جين في المحاكمة.
How did $50 turn into $10,000, anyway?
كيف تحول مبلغ 50 دولاراً إلى 10 آلاف دولار؟
Look, the officer's testimony is right here.
انظر، شهادة الضابط موجودة هنا.
"At 6:00 p.m. on April 27th,
"في الساعة 6:00 مساءً يوم 27 أبريل،
a Korean man gave me 10,000 dollars on my way home after work."
" أعطاني رجل كوري 10000 دولار في طريقي إلى المنزل بعد العمل."
After work? But we were there in daytime.
بعد العمل؟ ولكن كنا هناك في النهار.
I saw it happen. This is not right.
رأيتُ ذلك يحدث. هذا ليس صحيحًا.
I'm telling you, I saw him give the 50 dollars.
أنا أقول لك، لقد رأيته يعطي 50 دولارًا.
This must be why Ma-jin is getting a full trial.
لا بد أن هذا هو السبب وراء حصول ما جين على محاكمة كاملة.
Ha-neul, when's his trial?
ها-نول، متى محاكمته؟
It says "the day after tomorrow."
ويقول "بعد غد".
Look, Mr. Kang.
انظر، السيد كانغ.
This must be why we haven't received your helmets.
لا بد أن هذا هو السبب وراء عدم تلقينا خوذتك.
The authorities have seized them instead of clearing them.
قامت السلطات بمصادرتهم بدلاً من تطهيرهم.
What happens then?
ماذا يحدث بعد ذلك؟
If you fail to explain, they'll throw them out right away.
إذا فشلت في التوضيح، فسوف يطردونك على الفور.
They'll destroy them.
سوف يدمرونهم.
-That means we have 48 hours. -Why do you keep speaking English?
-هذا يعني أن لدينا 48 ساعة. -لماذا تستمر في التحدث باللغة الإنجليزية؟
So, what now? We've got to find a way out.
إذن، ماذا الآن؟ علينا إيجاد مخرج.
Everything's gone downhill.
كل شيء ذهب نحو الأسوأ.
Wait, that's Mr. Go's jacket.
انتظر، هذه سترة السيد جو.
Where did you get this jacket?
من أين حصلت على هذه السترة؟
I'm asking where you got this jacket.
أنا أسأل من أين حصلت على هذه السترة.
I don't know any Korean guy.
لا أعرف أي رجل كوري.
-Hey! -Stop!
-هي! -توقف!
Hold on. Let me explain.
انتظر، دعني أشرح لك.
Something's fishy. How did he know Mr. Go is a Korean?
هناك أمرٌ مريب. كيف عرف أن السيد غو كوري؟
-Hey, no, you're a foreigner. -Okay!
-لا، أنت أجنبي. -حسنًا!
-All right, but-- -Stop it!
-حسنًا، ولكن-- -توقف!
Listen, Mr. Kang.
إستمع، سيد كانغ.
"Friends?" They've come to see me?
"أصدقائي؟" لقد جاؤوا لرؤيتي؟
I'm too ashamed to face them.
أنا أشعر بالخجل الشديد من مواجهتهم.
What's going on with the helmets?
ماذا يحدث مع الخوذات؟
Hang on.
انتظر.
For just one minute. Just for a second or one minute.
لدقيقة واحدة فقط. لثانية واحدة أو دقيقة واحدة فقط.
What do we do if Mr. Go ends up serving time?
ماذا نفعل إذا انتهى الأمر بالسيد جو إلى قضاء فترة عقوبته في السجن؟
-I hear life in prison is brutal here. -Let's wait it out, Mr. Kang.
-سمعت أن الحياة في السجن قاسية هنا. -دعنا ننتظر، سيد كانج.
-Let's not go there just yet. -Excuse me.
- دعنا لا نذهب إلى هناك بعد. - عذرا.
Here, sir.
هنا سيدي.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
-Let's go. -Hey, Mr. Kang.
-لنذهب. -مرحبًا، سيد كانج.
-Mr. Go! -Where is he?
-سيد اذهب! -أين هو؟
Where is he?
أين هو؟
-Hey, Mr. Go! -There he is.
-يا سيد جو! -ها هو ذا.
-Where? -Over there. Mr. Go!
-أين؟ -هناك. اذهب يا سيد!
Mr. Go! We're over here!
سيد جو! نحن هنا!
-We're here. -Mr. Go!
-نحن هنا. -سيد اذهب!
-We're right here, Mr. Go!
-سيدي انطلق! -نحن هنا، سيدي انطلق!
-Over here, Mr. Go! -Ms. Oh!
-هنا، سيد جو! -سيدة أوه!
Mr. Kang!
السيد كانغ!
Mr. Go!
السيد اذهب!
Where's your top? I mean, what happened to your jacket?
أين قميصك؟ أعني، ماذا حدث لسترتك؟
I don't know. Someone must've stolen it.
لا أعلم، لا بد أن أحدهم سرقها.
I look awful, don't I?
أنا أبدو فظيعة، أليس كذلك؟
No, you don't.
لا، لا تفعل ذلك.
You look like your usual self. You seem fine.
تبدو كعادتك، تبدو بخير.
Hang in there, Mr. Go.
استمر في الصمود يا سيد جو.
Have you had anything to eat?
هل أكلت شيئا؟
I'm going to eat when I get released!
سوف آكل عندما يتم إطلاق سراحي!
We've only got five minutes left. Reassure him or something, Mr. Kang.
لم يتبقَّ سوى خمس دقائق. طمئنه يا سيد كانغ.
Mr. Go!
السيد اذهب!
We'll get you out of there!
سوف نخرجك من هناك!
Don't worry about a thing.
لا تقلق بشأن أي شيء.
What about the deal?
ماذا عن الصفقة؟
Don't stress about it!
لا تقلق بشأن هذا الأمر!
It's all going to be fine.
كل شيء سيكون على ما يرام.
Don't you worry about me.
لا تقلق علي.
I served in the Marines, dang it!
لقد خدمت في البحرية، اللعنة!
All right. Don't you worry about us.
حسنًا، لا تقلق علينا.
We'll get you out no matter what.
سوف نخرجك مهما كان الأمر.
-I'll be fine here. -Make sure to eat, okay?
- سأكون بخير هنا. - تأكد من تناول الطعام، حسنًا؟
Don't forget to feed yourself!
لا تنسى أن تطعم نفسك!
-Keep your belly full, okay? -I'll be fine!
-احتفظ ببطنك ممتلئة، حسنًا؟ -سأكون بخير!
Off you go.
إذهب بعيدا.
Hey, Mi-seon!
مهلا، مي سون!
Ms. Oh!
السيدة أوه!
-Why does he want me? -Let's get over there.
-لماذا يريدني؟ -دعنا نذهب إلى هناك.
-I'm right here, Mr. Go. -Ms. Oh!
-أنا هنا، سيد جو. -سيدة أوه!
-What's wrong? -Mi-seon!
-ما الخطب؟ -مي سون!
I'm here, Mr. Go.
أنا هنا، سيد جو.
-Pick it up! -Wait.
-التقطها! -انتظر.
No! Off you go.
لا! اذهب بعيدا.
I got it. Don't worry.
لقد حصلت عليه. لا تقلق.
All right. See you.
حسناً، إلى اللقاء.
Make sure to eat, okay? Don't skip a meal. Sit tight.
تأكد من تناول الطعام، حسنًا؟ لا تفوت أي وجبة. اجلس بهدوء.
-I'll keep this safe. -Okay.
-سأحافظ على هذا في مكان آمن. -حسنًا.
Make sure to eat, Mr. Go.
تأكد من تناول الطعام، سيد جو.
Okay.
تمام.
-Okay. -Eat well!
-حسنًا. -تناول الطعام جيدًا!
-Get out! -Hang in there!
-اخرج! -تمسك هناك!
MANAGE OUR CLIENTS, SALES AND INVENTORY - YOUR SENIOR COLLEAGUE
إدارة عملائنا ومبيعاتنا ومخزوننا - زميلك الرئيسي
Manage…
يدير…
our clients, sales and inventory.
عملائنا، المبيعات والمخزون.
Your senior colleague.
زميلك الأكبر سنا.
"Clients, sales and inventory."
"العملاء والمبيعات والمخزون."
Those are the basics of sales.
هذه هي أساسيات المبيعات.
The basics of sales?
أساسيات المبيعات؟
Does it make you that happy?
هل يجعلك سعيدا إلى هذه الدرجة؟
It says "your senior colleague," Mr. Kang.
ويقول "زميلك الأكبر"، السيد كانج.
I now have a colleague, not just someone who bosses me around.
لقد أصبح لدي الآن زميل، وليس مجرد شخص يتحكم بي.
Ms. Oh.
السيدة أوه.
What are the basics of being a CEO?
ما هي أساسيات أن تكون الرئيس التنفيذي؟
Excuse me?
اعذرني؟
You now have the three basic items to manage.
أصبح لديك الآن ثلاثة عناصر أساسية لإدارتها.
But for me,
ولكن بالنسبة لي،
I don't know what I should manage.
لا أعرف ما الذي ينبغي لي أن أتعامل معه.
What would my father tell me to protect?
ماذا سيطلب مني والدي أن أحمي؟
The company, of course.
الشركة، بالطبع.
Mr. Kang!
السيد كانغ!
What about the deal?
ماذا عن الصفقة؟
Don't stress about it!
لا تقلق بشأن هذا الأمر!
Don't you worry about me.
لا تقلق علي.
I served in the Marines, dang it!
لقد خدمت في البحرية، اللعنة!
Take care then.
اعتني بنفسك إذن.
EPISODE 9 WALKING TO THE SKY
الحلقة 9: المشي نحو السماء
Mr. Go!
السيد اذهب!
Don't forget to feed yourself! Keep your belly full, okay?
لا تنسَ أن تطعم نفسك! اشبع بطنك، حسنًا؟
Are we still knee deep in the Korean War? Why is she so hung up on food?
هل ما زلنا غارقين في الحرب الكورية؟ لماذا تهتم بالطعام لهذه الدرجة؟
Mr. Go!
السيد اذهب!
We'll get you out of there!
سوف نخرجك من هناك!
Don't worry about a thing.
لا تقلق بشأن أي شيء.
That's the least I can do here.
هذا أقل ما أستطيع فعله هنا.
I'm the one who messed up.
أنا الذي أفسد الأمر.
You two are pretty chummy, aren't you?
أنتم الاثنان ودودون جدًا، أليس كذلك؟
I get it, but let me share.
لقد فهمت ذلك، ولكن اسمح لي أن أشارك.
Excuse me. Coming through.
عذراً، سأمر.
-Sorry. -Come help me out later.
-آسف. -تعال ساعدني لاحقًا.
Of course. I'll see you soon!
بالطبع. سأراك قريبًا!
Excuse me. Coming through.
عذراً، سأمر.
Oh, dear. Sorry about that.
يا عزيزي، آسف على ذلك.
Please excuse me.
أرجو المعذرة.
Coming through.
قادم من خلال.
Hello, sir.
أهلاً سيدي.
-Hey, keep it up. -Thank you.
-هي، استمر في ذلك. -شكرا لك.
Excuse me. Coming through.
عذراً، سأمر.
Hey.
يا.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
All newbies flounder on their first day. The work itself isn't hard.
جميع المبتدئين يتعثرون في يومهم الأول. العمل بحد ذاته ليس صعبًا.
Everybody else works for a living too.
الجميع يعملون لكسب لقمة العيش أيضًا.
Go easy, will you?
اذهب بسهولة، أليس كذلك؟
Okay. I'll page you when I clock out.
حسنًا، سأتصل بك عندما أغادر.
All right. Make sure to do that.
حسناً. تأكد من القيام بذلك.
Mi-ho. Don't you worry about me.
مي هو. لا تقلق عليّ.
Me, worried? You got it all wrong.
أنا قلق؟ لقد فهمت الأمر خطأً.
Sure. Just don't push yourself too far.
بالتأكيد. فقط لا تضغط على نفسك أكثر من اللازم.
All right. See you.
حسناً، إلى اللقاء.
Kisses.
قبلات.
Hey, new guy.
مرحبًا أيها الرجل الجديد.
-Did you say you can ride a motorcycle? -Yes.
-هل قلت أنك تستطيع ركوب الدراجة النارية؟ -نعم.
Do a quick delivery for me.
قم بالتسليم السريع بالنسبة لي.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Give me my money back.
أعطني أموالي مرة أخرى.
Who did this? What the hell is this?
من فعل هذا؟ ما هذا بحق الجحيم؟
-What on earth… -What a bunch of rascals.
- ماذا على الأرض... -يا لها من مجموعة من الأوغاد.
-I invested a heavy sum. What do I do now? -Let's leave now.
- استثمرتُ مبلغًا كبيرًا. ماذا أفعل الآن؟ - لنغادر الآن.
What do I do?
ماذا أفعل؟
How could this have happened?
كيف حدث هذا؟
-I'm penniless now. -I can't believe this.
-أنا بلا مال الآن. -لا أستطيع أن أصدق هذا.
What do I do about the lost money?
ماذا أفعل بشأن الأموال المفقودة؟
That money was my lifeline!
لقد كان هذا المال شريان حياتي!
Oh, dear. We're done for.
يا عزيزي، لقد انتهينا.
-Get over here quickly. -What I wouldn't do to those crooks!
- تعال إلى هنا بسرعة. - ما الذي لن أفعله بهؤلاء المحتالين!
How could the heavens allow this? Where would these bastards be holed up?
كيف للسماء أن تسمح بهذا؟ أين سيختبئ هؤلاء الأوغاد؟
-They took off with everything. -That money was everything to me.
-لقد هربوا بكل شيء. -كان هذا المال هو كل شيء بالنسبة لي.
How dare you take my precious money, you rotten bastards?
كيف تجرؤون على أخذ أموالي الثمينة، أيها الأوغاد الفاسدون؟
Those bastards…
هؤلاء الأوغاد...
-How am I supposed to go on? -What…
-كيف من المفترض أن أستمر؟ -ماذا...
My heart is breaking. What should I do now?
قلبي يتقطع. ماذا أفعل الآن؟
-Give me my money back. -Oh, all my money…
-أعيدوا لي أموالي. -أوه، كل أموالي...
This can't be true!
هذا لا يمكن أن يكون صحيحا!
-Drink some. -I will.
-اشرب بعضًا. -سأفعل.
You offered my company an invaluable opportunity.
لقد عرضت لشركتي فرصة لا تقدر بثمن.
My foolishness almost caused you and your company harm.
كاد حماقتي أن تسبب لك ولشركتك الأذى.
My sincerest apologies.
اعتذاري الصادق.
I'm glad you know of your foolishness.
يسعدني أنك تعرف حماقتك.
But I don't need your apology.
ولكنني لا أحتاج إلى اعتذارك.
In business,
في مجال الأعمال،
what you need is not an apology, but money.
ما تحتاجه ليس اعتذارًا، بل مالًا.
It's much better to hold onto feces than a fart.
من الأفضل بكثير التمسك بالبراز بدلاً من التمسك بالريح.
The saying that it's better to be holding onto something substantial,
المثل القائل بأنه من الأفضل التمسك بشيء جوهري،
even if it may seem useless.
حتى لو بدا الأمر عديم الفائدة.
I wanted to ask you something.
أردت أن أسألك شيئا.
Why Thailand?
لماذا تايلاند؟
I've always wondered if a quality product would have a universal appeal.
لقد تساءلت دائمًا عما إذا كان المنتج عالي الجودة سيكون له جاذبية عالمية.
Price concerns aside, if the helmets sell here,
بغض النظر عن مخاوف الأسعار، إذا تم بيع الخوذات هنا،
I can look forward to future opportunities in the Thai market.
أستطيع أن أتطلع إلى الفرص المستقبلية في السوق التايلاندية.
However, I can't work with a company that's caused problems.
ومع ذلك، لا أستطيع العمل مع شركة تسببت في مشاكل.
Thanks for your efforts.
شكرا على جهودكم.
Tae-poong.
تاي بونغ.
Well, no.
حسنا، لا.
Forget about opportunities and insights. We're here to sell the helmets.
انسَ الفرص والرؤى. نحن هنا لبيع الخوذات.
-Go ask her to take some off our hands. -What?
-اذهب واطلب منها أن تأخذ بعضًا من أيدينا. -ماذا؟
It looks like she has a soft spot for you. Go on and put your skills to good use.
يبدو أنها تُحبك. هيا، استغل مهاراتك جيدًا.
-My skills? -You know what I'm talking about.
-مهاراتي؟ -أنت تعرف ما أتحدث عنه.
Tell her she's pretty and write "wish coupon" on her palm.
أخبرها أنها جميلة واكتب "قسيمة أمنيات" على راحة يدها.
Go and chat with her before she leaves for her meal.
اذهب وتحدث معها قبل أن تذهب لتناول وجبتها.
This is it. She's on her way. Where are you going?
هذه هي. إنها في طريقها. إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Come on, why are you leaving?
هيا، لماذا تغادر؟
-Get in here already. -But still…
- ادخل هنا بالفعل. - ولكن لا يزال...
Fine.
بخير.
I don't go around telling people they're pretty.
أنا لا أتجول وأخبر الناس أنهم جميلون.
There we go. One, two.
ها نحن ذا. واحد، اثنان.
What's that?
ما هذا؟
-Is it a gift for me? -Yes.
-هل هي هدية لي؟ -نعم.
Inside are items from the US for potential future projects.
في الداخل توجد عناصر من الولايات المتحدة لمشاريع مستقبلية محتملة.
Really?
حقًا؟
Hang on, who's Katherine Kang?
انتظر، من هي كاثرين كانج؟
Oh, that's Aunt Kang Suk-ja in LA.
أوه، هذه العمة كانج سوك جا في لوس أنجلوس.
I can't wait.
لا استطيع الانتظار.
What's this? Does she take me for a common peddler?
ما هذا؟ هل تعتبرني بائعًا متجولًا عاديًا؟
Does she seriously expect me to sell these?
هل تتوقع حقًا مني أن أبيع هذه الأشياء؟
All this common stuff?
كل هذه الأشياء المشتركة؟
I can't believe this.
لا أستطيع أن أصدق هذا.
What even is this mess?
ما هذه الفوضى؟
A shirt.
قميص.
How unsophisticated.
كم هو غير متطور.
Jeez.
جيز.
That aside, why did that idiot, Tae-poong, fly to Thailand?
بصرف النظر عن ذلك، لماذا طار هذا الأحمق، تاي بونج، إلى تايلاند؟
Oh, he went to Thailand to export Korean helmets.
أوه، لقد ذهب إلى تايلاند لتصدير الخوذات الكورية.
He sure loves safety gear and shit.
إنه بالتأكيد يحب معدات السلامة والأشياء الأخرى.
Enough about him.
كفى عنه.
What should I do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
Why won't my dad make any investments?
لماذا لا يقوم والدي بأي استثمارات؟
Why did he have to kick up the dust about buying those expensive ships?
لماذا كان عليه أن يثير الغبار حول شراء تلك السفن الباهظة الثمن؟
He drives me insane.
إنه يجعلني مجنونًا.
Wait, Mr. Ha.
انتظر، سيد ها.
What does my dad have against Typhoon Trading?
ما هو موقف والدي ضد شركة Typhoon Trading؟
As for me,
أما بالنسبة لي،
I want Tae-poong ruined for getting in my way ever since we were eight.
أريد تدمير تاي بونغ بسبب وقوفه في طريقي منذ أن كنا في الثامنة من عمرنا.
I just don't understand it.
انا لا أفهم ذلك.
Don't you find it odd?
ألا تجد هذا غريبا؟
The company didn't have much.
الشركة لم يكن لديها الكثير.
I wouldn't dare to presume what your father might be thinking,
لا أجرؤ على افتراض ما قد يفكر فيه والدك،
but he has no interest in such a trifling company.
لكن ليس لديه أي اهتمام بمثل هذه الشركة التافهة.
Goodness, it's late. I should return to my office.
يا إلهي، الوقت متأخر. يجب أن أعود إلى مكتبي.
TYPHOON TRADING
تايفون للتجارة
EMPLOYMENT RECORD CARD CHA SEON-TAEK
بطاقة سجل التوظيف تشا سيون تايك
OH MI-SEON
أوه مي سون
KOO MYUNG-GWAN
كو ميونغ غوان
That's more like it.
هذا هو أكثر مثل ذلك.
We could use an insurance of sorts.
نحن بحاجة إلى نوع من التأمين.
BAE SONG-JUNG
باي سونغ جونغ
GO MA-JIN
اذهب ما جين
Your son has asked me about the Typhoon Trading business.
لقد سألني ابنك عن أعمال شركة تايفون للتجارة.
Hyun-jun doesn't need to know, does he?
هيون جون لا يحتاج إلى معرفة، أليس كذلك؟
-Understood. -Dad!
-مفهوم. -أبي!
I found it, Dad.
لقد وجدته يا أبي.
I did it.
أنا فعلت هذا.
Dad.
أب.
Look.
ينظر.
Why don't I try selling this?
لماذا لا أحاول بيع هذا؟
What do you think? Isn't it awesome?
ما رأيك؟ أليس رائعًا؟
Have you given a thought to how you would sell it?
هل فكرت في كيفية بيعه؟
Why would I bother with that?
لماذا أهتم بهذا؟
You brought in eggheads and pay them a fortune to sort that out.
لقد جلبت أشخاصًا ذوي عقول مثقفة ودفعت لهم ثروة لحل هذه المشكلة.
Even so, the final call is your responsibility.
ومع ذلك، فإن القرار النهائي هو مسؤوليتك.
TYPHOON TRADING EMPLOYMENT RECORD CARD
بطاقة سجل التوظيف في شركة تايفون تريدينج
Are you sure you're not hungry?
هل أنت متأكد أنك لست جائعا؟
I have no appetite.
ليس لدي شهية.
Have you called your family?
هل اتصلت بعائلتك؟
No.
لا.
You know,
أنت تعرف،
Tae-poong…
في وقت متأخر من الليل…
Are we finally on a first-name basis?
هل أصبحنا أخيرا على علاقة بالاسم الأول؟
Unbelievable.
لا يصدق.
Are you still mad?
هل مازلت مجنونا؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I was too focused on securing a deal as a sales representative.
لقد كنت مهتمًا جدًا بتأمين صفقة كممثل مبيعات.
I wish you'd pay more attention to how I'd feel.
أتمنى أن تولي اهتماما أكبر لكيفية شعوري.
Wait a moment.
انتظر لحظة.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Could I have two watermelon smoothies?
هل يمكنني الحصول على اثنين من عصائر البطيخ؟
Sure, just a moment.
بالتأكيد، فقط لحظة.
Here, drink this.
تفضل، اشرب هذا.
This is watermelon juice.
هذا هو عصير البطيخ.
It's sweet.
إنه حلو.
Even when we're worried sick, we shouldn't skip a meal.
حتى عندما نشعر بالقلق والمرض، لا ينبغي لنا أن نتخطى وجبة الطعام.
Come on, I'm not worried sick.
تعال، أنا لست قلقًا جدًا.
I didn't know you could make juice out of watermelon.
لم أكن أعلم أنه بإمكانك صنع عصير من البطيخ.
It's amazing.
إنه أمر مدهش.
Mi-ho loves watermelons.
مي هو تحب البطيخ.
Do you miss her?
هل تفتقدها؟
You should give her a call. Don't worry about the phone bill.
اتصل بها. لا تقلق بشأن فاتورة الهاتف.
Tell you what.
سأخبرك ماذا.
I've never stayed apart from my family before.
لم أبتعد عن عائلتي أبدًا من قبل.
So, I miss Beom dearly and wonder how Mi-ho is doing.
لذا، أفتقد بوم بشدة وأتساءل كيف حال مي هو.
My grandmother has been on my mind too.
لقد كانت جدتي في ذهني أيضًا.
But I actually find this freeing.
ولكنني أجد هذا الأمر في الواقع محرراً.
Now that I'm alone, I feel like a weight has been lifted off my chest.
الآن بعد أن أصبحت وحدي، أشعر وكأن ثقلاً قد رفع عن صدري.
The idea of a business trip excited me as well.
لقد أثارتني فكرة رحلة العمل أيضًا.
Maybe that's why I insisted on coming, even when I knew Mr. Go hated it.
ربما هذا هو السبب الذي جعلني أصر على المجيء، حتى عندما كنت أعلم أن السيد جو يكره ذلك.
I'm a terrible person, aren't I?
أنا شخص فظيع، أليس كذلك؟
Sure, you're awful. What a surprise.
بالتأكيد، أنت فظيع. يا لها من مفاجأة!
Still, I like it.
لا يزال يعجبني ذلك.
When you're being mean.
عندما تكون سيئا.
Think about it. A person can't be good all the time.
فكر في الأمر. لا يمكن للإنسان أن يكون جيدًا طوال الوقت.
Anyone would think someone is a nice person
أي شخص يعتقد أن شخصًا ما هو شخص لطيف
if they are good 70% of the time and bad 30% of the time.
إذا كانوا جيدين 70% من الوقت وسيئين 30% من الوقت.
But you're mean only 10% of the time,
لكنك تعني 10% فقط من الوقت،
which was on this trip.
الذي كان في هذه الرحلة.
You think I'm a wimp, don't you?
هل تعتقد أنني ضعيف؟
You are…
أنت…
brilliant.
باهِر.
Out of all the people I've met,
من بين كل الأشخاص الذين التقيت بهم،
you're the coolest…
أنت الأروع
and the prettiest.
والأجمل.
Aren't you lucky to have me crushing on you?
أليس من حسن حظك أني معجب بك؟
Don't you want to?
ألا تريد ذلك؟
Come on, Mr. Kang!
تعال يا سيد كانج!
You're being silly.
أنت سخيف.
This isn't the time for this.
هذا ليس الوقت المناسب لذلك.
What are you objecting to?
على ماذا تعترض؟
Don't get so up close and personal.
لا تقترب من الأمر كثيراً وشخصياً.
-Why not? -I don't feel comfortable.
-لماذا لا؟ -لا أشعر بالراحة.
You don't feel comfortable?
ألا تشعر بالراحة؟
At any rate, Mr. Go is facing possible jail time.
على أي حال، السيد جو يواجه احتمال الحكم عليه بالسجن.
We shouldn't be wasting our time on our personal matters.
لا ينبغي لنا أن نضيع وقتنا في أمورنا الشخصية.
We've got a serious situation here.
لدينا وضع خطير هنا.
By the way, why do you think the customs officer falsely accused Mr. Go
بالمناسبة، لماذا تعتقد أن موظف الجمارك اتهم السيد جو زوراً؟
of paying him $10,000?
من دفع له 10000 دولار؟
He must've wanted to get someone else off the hook.
لا بد أنه أراد تخليص شخص آخر من هذا المأزق.
Mr. Go's bribe was only about $50.
كانت رشوة السيد جو حوالي 50 دولارًا فقط.
Could the officer have lied to get the man with Mr. Go's jacket released?
هل يمكن للضابط أن يكذب لإطلاق سراح الرجل الذي يرتدي سترة السيد جو؟
We don't know how he got hold of that jacket,
نحن لا نعرف كيف حصل على تلك السترة،
but he must've pretended to be Mr. Go.
لكن لا بد أنه تظاهر بأنه السيد جو.
Mr. Go's trial is tomorrow.
محاكمة السيد جو غدا.
I'll have to secure the money to pay his bail.
سوف يتوجب علي تأمين المال لدفع الكفالة.
Do we have enough funds, though?
هل لدينا ما يكفي من الأموال؟
I've called colleagues in Korea to gather what funds they can.
لقد اتصلت بزملائي في كوريا لجمع ما يمكنهم من الأموال.
Let's do all we can to get him out on bail tomorrow.
دعونا نفعل كل ما بوسعنا لإخراجه بكفالة غدًا.
I should've done more to stop him instead of taking photos.
كان ينبغي لي أن أفعل المزيد لإيقافه بدلاً من التقاط الصور.
Tell me. Did you really hate it?
أخبرني هل كرهته حقًا؟
Right, the photos!
تمام ، الصور!
Come on!
تعال!
Here they are.
ها هم هنا.
You finished two rolls of film in that short time?
لقد انتهيت من لفافتين من الفيلم في هذا الوقت القصير؟
Three rolls, actually.
ثلاث لفات، في الواقع.
Each only had 24 shots, anyway. We need the photos for our trip report.
على أي حال، كان لدى كلٍّ منهما ٢٤ لقطة فقط. نحتاج الصور لتقرير رحلتنا.
I recorded pretty much all the events of the day.
لقد قمت بتسجيل جميع أحداث اليوم تقريبًا .
Records remain while memories fade.
تبقى السجلات بينما تتلاشى الذكريات.
Hey, that's a cool line.
مهلا، هذا خط رائع.
It's what your father used to say.
هذا ما كان والدك يقوله.
I think I photographed the incident. No, I'm sure of it.
أعتقد أنني صوّرتُ الحادثة. لا، أنا متأكد من ذلك.
Mr. Go handed over the cigarette packs and slipped the 50-dollar bill inside.
سلم السيد جو علب السجائر ووضع ورقة الخمسين دولارًا في الداخل.
I can't believe you took photos of that.
لا أستطيع أن أصدق أنك التقطت صورًا لذلك.
Why did you do it, though?
ولكن لماذا فعلت ذلك؟
Because he went against the company code.
لأنه خالف قانون الشركة.
I see.
أرى.
Where can we go to get these developed? We can't wait around until tomorrow.
أين يمكننا تطوير هذه؟ لا نطيق الانتظار حتى الغد.
It's 9:30 p.m.
الساعة 9:30 مساءً
Mr. Go's trial is at 11:00 a.m. and the helmets will be scrapped at 4:00 p.m.
محاكمة السيد جو ستكون في الساعة 11:00 صباحًا وسيتم إلغاء الخوذات في الساعة 4:00 مساءً
We have to clear Mr. Go's name before that, no matter what.
يتعين علينا تبرئة اسم السيد جو قبل ذلك، مهما كان الأمر.
Let's go look for a photo studio.
دعنا نذهب للبحث عن استديو التصوير.
-All right. -Let's go.
-حسنًا. -لنذهب.
-Where should we go? -Over there, I suppose?
-أين يجب أن نذهب؟ -هناك، على ما أعتقد؟
Hi. Hello.
مرحبا. مرحبا.
-Well, photo… -Photo… Print.
-حسنًا، صورة... -صورة... اطبع.
-Okay. -Okay, thank you.
-حسنًا. -حسنًا، شكرًا لك.
Like so…
مثل ذلك…
Oh, no.
أوه لا.
-We've got films here. We want photos. -Photo films.
-لدينا أفلام هنا. نريد صورًا. -أفلام مصورة.
-Okay, thank you. -Okay.
-حسنًا، شكرًا لك. -حسنًا.
Gosh.
يا إلهي.
Where can we…
أين يمكننا…
I don't see anything.
لا أرى شيئا.
-Let's ask him and call it a day. -Okay.
-دعنا نسأله وننهي هذا اليوم. -حسنًا.
-Hi. Hello. -Hello.
-مرحبا. مرحبا. -مرحبا.
-Yes, photo and film. -Oh, photo.
-نعم، الصورة والفيلم. -أوه، الصورة.
-Saphan? Bridge. -Yes.
-صافان؟ جسر. -نعم.
-Is there a studio? -Just across the bridge.
-هل يوجد استوديو؟ -بالقرب من الجسر.
-Thank you. -Thank you so much.
-شكرا جزيلا.
Hey, look over there!
مهلا، انظر هناك!
It says "photo."
يقول "صورة".
-Film… Look inside. -Okay.
-فيلم... انظر إلى الداخل. -حسنًا.
-Excuse me!
-عفوا!
-Hello? -Is anyone there?
-مرحبا؟ -هل يوجد أحد هناك؟
-Please! -Help me!
-من فضلك! -ساعدني!
-I'm in a rush! Hello? -Hello? Is no one there?
-أنا مستعجل! أهلًا؟ -أهلًا؟ ما في أحد هنا؟
-Hello. -No.
-مرحبا. -لا.
-Thank you. -Wrong again.
-شكرا لك. -خطأ مرة أخرى.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
-Please. -Excuse me.
-من فضلك. -عفوا.
Could you call the owner…
هل يمكنك الاتصال بالمالك؟
-Photo… -I guess she doesn't run the studio.
-صورة... -أعتقد أنها لا تدير الاستوديو.
-Dang, what do we do now? -I'm losing my mind.
- يا إلهي، ماذا نفعل الآن؟ - لقد فقدت عقلي.
Maybe it's time for us to give up.
ربما حان الوقت لنا للتخلي.
What can we do when there are no photo studios?
ماذا يمكننا أن نفعل عندما لا يكون هناك استوديوهات للتصوير؟
We need to cause a scene to have people call the studio owner.
نحن بحاجة إلى إحداث مشهد يدفع الناس إلى الاتصال بمالك الاستوديو.
-Shall I kick down the door? -What?
-هل أركل الباب؟ -ماذا؟
-I'll do it. -Hold on.
-سأفعل ذلك. -انتظر.
Let's think of another way. Don't.
دعنا نفكر بطريقة أخرى. لا تفعل.
They'll open the shop if the police get here.
سيفتحون المتجر إذا وصلت الشرطة هنا.
Don't do it. Give me a second.
لا تفعل ذلك. أعطني ثانية.
This isn't the way. My gosh!
هذه ليست الطريقة. يا إلهي!
Seriously? Wait!
بجدية؟ انتظر!
-Hello.
-مرحبا.
-Good evening. -Could you open the door?
-مساء الخير. -هل يمكنك فتح الباب؟
How long will it take?
كم من الوقت سوف يستغرق؟
-Three. -Three hours?
-ثلاثة. -ثلاث ساعات؟
-Three hours? Then…
-ثلاث ساعات؟ ثم...
That would be 2 a.m.
سيكون ذلك في الساعة الثانية صباحًا
Will it be done by 2 a.m.?
هل سيتم ذلك بحلول الساعة الثانية صباحًا؟
-What did he say? -No idea.
-ماذا قال؟ -لا أعرف.
MAY 2ND, 1998
2 مايو 1998
We have to wait until then?
هل علينا أن ننتظر حتى ذلك الحين؟
A whopping three days? Three days?
ثلاثة أيام كاملة؟ ثلاثة أيام؟
Three days?
ثلاثة أيام؟
-Yes. -No.
-نعم.-لا. ​
No, no.
لا لا.
One, two, three.
واحد اثنين ثلاثة.
Forget it!
انسى ذلك!
-Wait, wait. -Hang on.
-انتظر، انتظر. -انتظر.
Okay.
تمام.
Okay. So…
حسنًا. إذًا...
How much do you want?
كم تريد؟
We'll offer…
سنقدم…
-There. 1,000 baht. -Okay.
-هناك. 1000 بات. -حسنا.
Thousand. 1,000 baht.
ألف و1000 بات.
What? He struck off a day?
ماذا؟ هل شطب يومًا؟
-There. -Two thousand.
-هناك. -ألفين.
I can't believe this. So?
لا أستطيع تصديق هذا. ماذا؟
-Still not satisfied? -Go, go, go, go.
-مازلت غير راضي؟ -اذهب، اذهب، اذهب، اذهب.
He's driving me crazy.
إنه يقودني إلى الجنون.
What are you doing, Ms. Oh? No, I can't lose this!
ماذا تفعلين يا آنسة؟ لا، لا أستطيع أن أخسر هذا!
How come? Was it your father's?
كيف ذلك؟ هل كان لوالدك؟
I only brought one watch.
لقد أحضرت ساعة واحدة فقط.
Take it off. You know we haven't got time for this.
انزعها، أنت تعلم أنه ليس لدينا وقت لهذا.
-But it's… -Hurry!
-لكن... -أسرع!
Do we have a deal? You can have this on top of 3,000 baht.
هل لدينا اتفاق؟ يمكنك الحصول على هذا بالإضافة إلى ٣٠٠٠ بات.
-Deal? -Sure.
-اتفاق؟ -بالتأكيد.
All right, sure.
حسناً، بالتأكيد.
Gosh, seriously?
يا إلهي، بجد؟
What's this? Has the power gone out?
ما هذا؟ هل انقطعت الكهرباء؟
He turned the lights off to get the photos developed.
أطفأ الأضواء حتى يتمكن من تطوير الصور.
Oh, right.
أوه، صحيح.
We're on the right track then.
نحن على الطريق الصحيح إذن.
What time is it, anyway?
ما هو الوقت على أية حال؟
I don't have my watch with me.
ليس لدي ساعتي معي.
BELLUA DEPARTMENT STORE
متجر بيلوا
CLEARANCE SALE
بيع التصفية
I guess he's not coming today.
أعتقد أنه لن يأتي اليوم.
Hey, you're here.
مهلا، أنت هنا.
My shift ended later than usual.
انتهت نوبتي في وقت متأخر عن المعتاد.
I couldn't reach the department store in time, so I came here.
لم أستطع الوصول إلى المتجر في الوقت المناسب، لذا أتيت إلى هنا.
Sorry.
آسف.
Let's go. I'll walk you home.
دعنا نذهب. سأوصلك إلى المنزل.
Okay.
تمام.
We're here already.
نحن هنا بالفعل.
You must be tired. Go in and rest.
لا بد أنك متعب. ادخل واسترح.
Hey.
يا.
-Yeah? -What's the matter?
-نعم؟ -ما الأمر؟
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Mi-ho, it's just that…
مي هو، إنه فقط...
This won't do. Let me take a few more steps back.
هذا لن يُجدي نفعًا. دعني أتراجع بضع خطوات أخرى.
My family had to close down the pub today.
اضطرت عائلتي إلى إغلاق الحانة اليوم.
Things somehow turned out that way.
لقد تحولت الأمور بطريقة ما بهذه الطريقة.
We had to put our place on sale…
لقد كان علينا أن نطرح مكاننا للبيع...
We'll probably have to crash with my aunt for the time being.
ربما يتعين علينا أن نقيم مع خالتي في الوقت الحالي.
And?
و؟
I just thought
لقد فكرت فقط
I should tell you.
ينبغي لي أن أخبرك.
You're not supposed to keep a secret from the person you're seeing.
لا ينبغي لك أن تخفي سرًا عن الشخص الذي تلتقي به.
And why did you step away to tell me that?
ولماذا ابتعدت لتخبرني بذلك؟
I didn't want my sorrow
لم أكن أريد حزني
to taint you.
لتلويثك.
You dummy.
يا غبي.
Cut out the melodrama.
اقطع الدراما.
Just tell me it's rough for you.
فقط أخبرني أن الأمر صعب بالنسبة لك.
Be frank and ask me to stay by your side.
كن صريحًا واطلب مني البقاء بجانبك.
Okay.
تمام.
Look at these.
أنظر إلى هؤلاء.
-Hey, we've got our photos. -Yeah.
-مرحبًا، لقد حصلنا على صورنا. -نعم.
Thank goodness.
شكرا لله.
SAWADDEE
سوادي
They'll be ready soon.
سيكونون جاهزين قريبا.
Meet me at the court. I'll go get the money and the documents.
قابلني في المحكمة. سأذهب لأحضر المال والوثائق.
The money?
المال؟
We don't know how much the fine will be, so…
نحن لا نعلم كم ستكون الغرامة، لذلك…
-Okay. -Be careful on your way, all right?
-حسنًا. - كن حذرًا في طريقك، حسنًا؟
-Sure. See you later. -Okay.
-بالتأكيد. أراك لاحقًا. -حسنًا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
MIN BURI CRIMINAL COURT MIN BURI CIVIL COURT
محكمة مين بوري الجنائية محكمة مين بوري المدنية
Hey, there comes Ma-jin.
مهلا، ها هو ما جين قادم.
He looks better than I hoped.
إنه يبدو أفضل مما كنت أتمنى.
By the way, where is Ms. Oh?
بالمناسبة، أين السيدة أوه؟
She should be here by now.
ينبغي أن تكون هنا الآن.
All rise.
الجميع ينهضون.
You can sit back down now.
يمكنك الجلوس مرة أخرى الآن.
What do I do? Oh, no!
ماذا أفعل؟ أوه، لا!
What should I do now?
ماذا يجب أن أفعل الآن؟
Damn, you've got to be kidding me.
يا لعنة، أنت تمزح معي.
I deeply regret that, as a foreign national,
أشعر بالأسف الشديد لأنني، كمواطن أجنبي،
you have attempted to undermine the laws of this country.
لقد حاولت تقويض قوانين هذا البلد.
While there is some dispute regarding the amount of the bribe,
في حين أن هناك بعض الخلاف فيما يتعلق بمبلغ الرشوة،
The ruling is based on the $10,000 stated in the witness's testimony.
ويستند الحكم على مبلغ العشرة آلاف دولار المذكور في شهادة الشاهد.
So…
لذا…
I'll talk to her.
سأتحدث معها.
"Evidence," so proof?
"الدليل" إذن دليل؟
I don't have such a big sum…
ليس لدي مثل هذا المبلغ الكبير...
Please ask her how I'm supposed to prove that I'm broke.
من فضلك اسألها كيف يمكنني أن أثبت أنني مفلس.
Then, I will deliver the verdict.
ومن ثم سأصدر الحكم.
We have evidence!
لدينا الدليل!
Could you interpret for me?
هل يمكنك أن تترجم لي؟
Even the total price of the helmets we brought is nowhere near $10,000.
حتى السعر الإجمالي للخوذات التي أحضرناها لا يصل إلى 10 آلاف دولار.
Why would we use that much for a bribe?
لماذا نستخدم هذا المبلغ للرشوة؟
I also brought
لقد أحضرت أيضا
the import declaration form and the quotation we've sent
نموذج إعلان الاستيراد والعرض الذي أرسلناه
the Nihakham Group by fax.
مجموعة نيهكهام بالفاكس.
What's more,
وما هو أكثر من ذلك،
I have the purchase agreement.
لدي اتفاقية شراء.
You have a point.
لديك وجهة نظر.
But… this is insufficient as direct evidence.
ولكن... هذا لا يكفي كدليل مباشر.
You may have had…
ربما كان لديك...
I think she's saying that the documents don't qualify as conclusive proof.
I think she's saying that the documents don't qualify as conclusive proof.
More… So…
More… So…
Well…
Well…
We…
We…
How should I say this…
How should I say this…
-Are you okay? -The photos…
-Are you okay? -The photos…
The photos fell under the bridge.
The photos fell under the bridge.
I tried to get them out of the water, but all we've got are these films.
I tried to get them out of the water, but all we've got are these films.
What do we do?
What do we do?
I'm sorry. I don't know what to do.
I'm sorry. I don't know what to do.
It's all good. You did a good job.
It's all good. You did a good job.
-Are you unhurt? -Yes, I'm good.
-Are you unhurt? -Yes, I'm good.
What do we do? I'm so sorry.
What do we do? I'm so sorry.
Don't apologize.
Don't apologize.
We've got these, at least.
We've got these, at least.
The film…
The film…
Turn the lights off on my signal, okay?
Turn the lights off on my signal, okay?
Okay.
Okay.
What on earth?
What on earth?
I'd get 30 years, wouldn't I?
I'd get 30 years, wouldn't I?
WALKING TO THE SKY
WALKING TO THE SKY
TYPHOON FAMILY
TYPHOON FAMILY
Our helmets will be disposed of if this case isn't closed by 4:00.
Our helmets will be disposed of if this case isn't closed by 4:00.
It'll take at least an hour to get to the port.
It'll take at least an hour to get to the port.
I have something to tell you.
I have something to tell you.
Thank you.
Thank you.
I thought about it and realized I never said this.
I thought about it and realized I never said this.
I was just doing my job,
I was just doing my job,
whenever I had to do it.
whenever I had to do it.
-We aren't going to work? -Well, we are.
-We aren't going to work? -Well, we are.
But we aren't going in that direction.
But we aren't going in that direction.
This is Typhoon Trading version 2.0.
This is Typhoon Trading version 2.0.
"Notice of Office Relocation."
"Notice of Office Relocation."
I'll be back.
I'll be back.
I promise.
I promise.
Subtitle translation by: Jeongwoo Kim
Subtitle translation by: Jeongwoo Kim